[

](https://wandb.ai/site)

* Platform
    
    Close Platform Open Platform

    * [Experiments  
        Track and visualize your ML experiments](https://wandb.ai/site/experiment-tracking/)
    * [Sweeps  
        Optimize your hyperparameters](https://wandb.ai/site/sweeps/)
    * [Registry  
        Publish and share your ML models and datasets](https://wandb.ai/site/registry/)
    * [Automations  
        Trigger workflows automatically](https://wandb.ai/site/automations/)

    * [Traces  
        Explore and debug LLM applications](https://wandb.ai/site/traces/)
    * [Evaluations  
        Rigorous evaluations of GenAI applications](https://wandb.ai/site/evaluations/)
    
    Core platform
    
    * [Artifacts  
        Version and manage your ML pipelines](https://wandb.ai/site/artifacts/)
    * [Tables  
        Visualize and explore your ML data](https://wandb.ai/site/tables/)
    * [Reports  
        Document and share your ML insights](https://wandb.ai/site/reports/)
    * [SDK  
        Log ML experiments and artifacts at scale](https://wandb.ai/site/sdk/)
    
* Solutions
    
    Close Solutions Open Solutions
    
    ##### Use cases

    ##### Industries

* Enterprise
    
    Close Enterprise Open Enterprise

* Resources
    
    Close Resources Open Resources

* Company
    
    Close Company Open Company

### [Weights & Biases Legal](https://wandb.ai/site/legal-home)

Privacy Policy
==============

Last updated: August 1, 2024

Thanks for your interest in Weights and Biases! We are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes how Weights and Biases, Inc. (“W&B”, “we”, “us” or “our”) collect, use, retain, disclose and protect personal information, and your rights in respect of your personal information. This Privacy Policy applies to information collected when you access our website located at [https://wandb.ai](https://wandb.ai/), including all subdomains (“Website”), when you use our products and services (collectively, “W&B Services”), attend our events or otherwise interact with us.

This Privacy Policy supplements other notices we may provide regarding the collection or processing of personal information. If you use W&B Services and have a separate agreement with W&B, then the terms of that agreement will supersede this Privacy Policy where the terms overlap.

**1\. Collection of Information** 

We collect personal information about you in the following ways:

1\. Information you provide  
We collect information that you directly provide to W&B when you access or use our Website or W&B Services.

2\. Information we collect automatically  
We collect information about you automatically when you access or use our Website or W&B Services. 

3\. Information we collect from third parties  
We collect information about you from third parties, including business partners, event organizers, and professional networking sites.  

See details

1. Information you provide  
      
    You may choose to provide us with personal information when you use our Website or W&B Services.  The types of personal information you may provide voluntarily include:  
      
    * Personal information you provide when you create an account, download, install, access or use W&B Services, sign up for our marketing materials, request customer support, communicate with us through online chat applications, make a purchase, register for white papers, web seminars or events, participate in surveys or contests or apply for a job at W&B. This may include your name, username, password, picture, title, role, email, phone number, company name and details of your company.  

    * Personal information you provide to when you purchase W&B Services through our Website or by contacting us directly. This may include information about the payment amount, payment method, shipping information, billing address, contact information, date of purchase and purchase history. You may be required to provide your credit card details to Stripe, our third-party payment processor operating as our agent. Payment processing services by Stripe are subject to the Stripe’s security and privacy policies found on Stripe’s website. As a condition of W&B enabling payment processing services through Stripe, you authorize W&B to share registration and transaction information related to your use of the payment processing services provided by Stripe.  

    * Personal information relating to any correspondence you send us, when you engage with us through online chat applications, provide us feedback, submit a response to an employment opportunity, post messages on message boards on our Website or use W&B Services. This may include information such as the content, subject, sender, recipient and date.  

    * If you invite a third party to use W&B Services, we may collect the name and email address of such third party in order to invite them to collaborate.  

2. Information we collect automatically  
      
    When you visit our Website or use W&B Services, we may collect personal information automatically. The types of personal information that we collect automatically include:  
      
    * Personal information relating to user activity on our Website and W&B Services, such as, but not limited to, applications and features you use, content you access, actions taken in connection with accessing our Website and W&B Services, access, event, diagnostic and other log files, usage, operational status, software errors and crash reports, authentication details, and quality and performance metrics. When you engage with us through online chat applications, we may record and review the chat in order to help address your questions.  

    * Personal information relating to visits to our Website and W&B Services from your computer or other devices, such as, but not limited to, your IP address, geographical location, browser type, internet service provider, website pages viewed, operating system, length of visit, time stamp of your visit, and referring website addresses.  
          
        We (and the service providers working on our behalf) may collect this personal information using cookies and similar technologies, including third-party usage tracking tools.  

3. Information we collect from third parties  
    
    In some cases, we may collect personal information about you from third parties, including business partners, event organizers, and professional networking sites. Please note that any third party that collects your information will have their own privacy policies governing how they use and protect your personal information. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of such third parties. 
    
    We will not intentionally collect and will never ask you to provide any information regarding your race or ethnicity, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, sexual orientation, trade union membership, information about your health, genetic and biometric data, or any other sensitive information.

**2\. Use of Information**

We use the personal information we collect about you to provide and support our Website and W&B Services and respond to your requests.

See details

We use the personal information we collect about you for the following reasons:

* To develop, provide, operate, support and maintain our Website and W&B Services;
    
* To generate analytics for the purpose of better understanding how our visitors and customers use our Website and W&B Services;
    
* To send communications to you to confirm orders, respond to inquiries and provide notices and updates;
    
* To improve our user experience, Website and the W&B Services;
    
* To send you relevant website content and marketing communications including news, promotions, offers and advertisements for W&B Services;
    
* To enable you to participate in surveys, competition, events and to process and deliver entries and rewards;
    
* To enable you to apply for employment positions at W&B;
    
* To maintain the security of our Website and W&B Services, including to investigate and prevent suspicious activity, fraudulent behaviour, violations of our terms and policies and illegal activities;
    
* To confirm compliance with, and investigate violations of, our user restrictions and subscription plan limitations;
    
* To comply with the laws and regulations to which we are subject, including legal requirements to report to tax authorities and disclose information to law enforcement authorities.

We rely on the following legal basis to use your personal information: 

* We have your consent (which will be apparent from the context, because we will ask for you consent when you provide your personal information);
    
* it is necessary to perform a contract with you (for example, we must process your payments data in order to fulfil any order you place with us), in which case we will be unable to fulfil our contract with you if you do not provide necessary information;
    
* the use is within our legitimate interests and not adverse to your rights and freedoms (for example, to send you marketing communications, provided this is consistent with your communications preferences); or
    
* it is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation.

**3\. Disclosure of Information**

We may disclose your personal information to our affiliates, service providers, authorities, potential buyers and other third parties.

See details

We may disclose your personal information to the following categories of recipients:

* We may share your personal information with W&B Affiliates where this is necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. W&B Affiliates will at all times protect your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. “W&B Affiliates” means Weights and Biases Japan K.K.  

* We may share your personal information with third party companies who work on our behalf, including providers of data analytics services, data hosting services, marketing services, payment services, technical support services or other specific business services, and IT providers, insurers, and professional advisers.  

* We may share your personal information with any third-party applications or services that you choose to use in connection with W&B Services, including any integration partners.  

* We may share your personal information where we believe it is necessary to exercise, establish or defend legal claims, to protect the vital interests of any person, or to comply with an order or request from any competent court, regulator, law enforcement agency or government authority.  

* We may share your personal information to potential buyers in connection with any proposed purchase of any part of our business. We will inform the buyer to use your personal information only for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.  

* We will only transfer your personal information to other third parties, including event sponsors and resellers, with your consent or where we are required or permitted by law to do so.  

* We may share with third parties aggregated and anonymized information that does not directly identify you.

**4\. Protection of Personal Information**

We are committed to securing your personal information. We implement reasonable and appropriate technological and organizational measures to help protect your personal information from loss, misuse and unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction and we comply with applicable data protection laws and regulations.

**5\. Cookies**

We use cookies to provide our Website and W&B Services. If you do not want us to place a cookie on your hard drive, you may be able to turn that feature off on your computer or mobile device. Please consult your Internet browser’s documentation for information on how to do this. However, if you decide not to accept cookies from us, some features of our Website and W&B Services may not function properly.

**6\. Your Rights**

Data protection laws give individuals rights with respect to the collection and use of their personal information. Please fill out the information [here](https://preferences.wandb.ai/privacy?_gl=1*oflud4*_ga*MTY1MDMyMDUyMy4xNjkyNjI1NDg3*_ga_JH1SJHJQXJ*MTcwNzQ5MjAwNS4yOTAuMS4xNzA3NDkzNDQxLjMyLjAuMA..) if you wish to exercise any of these rights. We will fulfil any such requests in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

See details

Depending on the laws that apply in your country and to which we are subject, you may have rights under applicable data protection laws to:

* request access to, correction of, deletion of, or portability of personal information that we process about you;
* request that we restrict processing, or to object to our processing, of personal information about you;
* opt-out of marketing communications that we may send you, for example, by clicking on the unsubscribe link in any marketing emails;
* not be subject to wholly automated decisions if these have legal effects on you or significantly affect you; and
* if our processing is based on your consent, withdraw your consent to our processing (although this will not affect the lawfulness of our processing prior to your withdrawal).

In addition, you also have the right to complain to your local data protection authority about our use of your personal information. However, while you are not required to do so, we ask that you contact us first to give us the opportunity to address your concerns directly before speaking with your data protection authority.

**7\. Data Retention**

We store the personal information we collect for as long as is necessary for the purpose for which it was collected, including as long as is necessary to provide you with the Website or W&B Services, or as otherwise necessary to comply with applicable legal requirements.

When we have no ongoing need to use your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize it or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information is stored in backup archives), we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

**8\. International Transfers**

W&B is located in the United States, but we and our service providers operate in various countries around the world. For these reasons, when you visit our Website or use W&B Services, your personal information may be transferred to countries other than the country in which you reside. W&B will take all necessary measures to ensure that your personal information is protected in accordance with this Privacy Policy and that any such transfers are lawful, including through the use of standard contractual clauses. Additionally, we obtain contractual commitments from third party service providers to protect your personal information.

**9\. Additional Information**

Some countries may have specific requirements that apply when we transfer personal information internationally. Where this is the case, the requirements that apply and measures we take to comply with those requirements are described further here.

See details

If you are in the European Economic Area (“EEA”) or United Kingdom (“UK”), then please note the following additional information:

1\. Data controller

The data controller of your personal information is W&B.  You can contact us using the details provided herein.

2\. EEA/UK legal basis

We will collect and use your personal information only where:

* We have your consent (which will be apparent from the context, because we will ask for you consent when you provide your personal information);
* it is necessary to perform a contract with you (for example, we must process your payments data in order to fulfil any order you place with us), in which case we will be unable to fulfil our contract with you if you do not provide necessary information;
* the use is within our legitimate interests and not adverse to your rights and freedoms (for example, to send you marketing communications, provided this is consistent with your communications preferences); or
* it is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation.

As we may rely on different legal bases for each of the different categories of personal information we process and the purposes for which we process them, please contact us if you would like further information about the specific legal basis relied upon in any particular context.

3\. International Transfers

If we transfer your personal information to a country outside of the EEA (for EEA residents) or the UK (for UK residents), we will ensure that any such transfers are compliant with EU and UK data protection law, as applicable.

We will only transfer your personal information to a non-EEA or non-UK recipient where:

* The recipient is located in a country that the European Commission has decided is adequate to receive personal information from the EEA or the UK Secretary of State has decided is adequate to receive personal information from the UK, as applicable;
* The recipient has signed appropriate contractual terms with W&B that incorporate the European Commission’s [Standard Contractual Clauses](https://commission.europa.eu/publications/standard-contractual-clauses-international-transfers_en) or the UK Information Commissioner’s [International Data Transfer Agreement or International Data Transfer Addendum](https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/uk-gdpr-guidance-and-resources/international-transfers/international-data-transfer-agreement-and-guidance/), as applicable; or
* A data transfer derogation applies (for example, where you have consented to the transfer of your personal information).

For Japan, “W&B” in this Privacy Policy means Weights and Biases Japan K.K. We may provide personal information obtained for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy (“Purposes”) to third parties, including our affiliate, Weights and Biases, Inc. These third parties will only process personal information for fulfilling the Purposes. We will supervise the appropriate handling of personal data by such third parties.

‍Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to obtain certain information about the types of personal information that companies with whom they have an established business relationship (and that are not otherwise exempt) have shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year, including the names and addresses of those third parties, and examples of the types of services or products marketed by those third parties. If you wish to submit a request pursuant to Section 1798.83, please contact Weights and Biases via email at support@wandb.com.

If you have further questions about our international data transfers and the specific measures we use in any case, please contact us for further information.

**10\. Children**

Neither our Website nor W&B Services are intended for or advertised to children under 16. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect information about children under 16.

If you believe that we have collected information about a child under 16, please contact us using the details provided above so that we may delete the information.

**11\. Updates**

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time in response to changing legal, regulatory or operational requirements. We will provide notice of any such changes (including when they will take effect) in accordance with law. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy periodically to stay informed about our practices.

To see when this Privacy Policy was last updated, please see the “Last Updated” section at the outset of this Privacy Policy.

**12\. How to Contact Us**

If you have questions about our use of your personal information, please email us at [support@wandb.com](mailto:support@wandb.com). To submit a data subject request, please fill out the information [here](https://preferences.wandb.ai/privacy?_gl=1*oflud4*_ga*MTY1MDMyMDUyMy4xNjkyNjI1NDg3*_ga_JH1SJHJQXJ*MTcwNzQ5MjAwNS4yOTAuMS4xNzA3NDkzNDQxLjMyLjAuMA..).

[

](https://wandb.ai/site)

##### The Platform

##### Article

##### Resources

##### Company

Copyright © Weights & Biases. All rights reserved.

* Platform
    
    Close Platform Open Platform
    
    * [Experiments  
        Lightweight experiment tracking](https://wandb.ai/site/experiment-tracking/)
    * [Reports  
        Collaborative dashboards](https://wandb.ai/site/reports/)
    * [Artifacts  
        Dataset and model versioning](https://wandb.ai/site/artifacts/)
    * [Tables  
        Interactive data visualization](https://wandb.ai/site/tables/)
    * [Sweeps  
        Hyperparameter optimization](https://wandb.ai/site/sweeps/)
    * [Models  
        Centralized model registry](https://wandb.ai/site/models/)
    * [Launch  
        Automated ML workflows](https://wandb.ai/site/launch/)
    * [Prompts  
        LLMOps and prompt engineering](https://wandb.ai/site/prompts/)
    * [Monitoring  
        Observability for production ML](https://wandb.ai/site/monitoring/)
    * [Weave  
        Interactive ML app builder](https://wandb.ai/site/weave/)
    
* Solutions
    
    Close Solutions Open Solutions
    
    ##### Use cases

    ##### Industries

* Ecosystem
    
    Close Ecosystem Open Ecosystem

* Enterprise
    
    Close Enterprise Open Enterprise

* Company
    
    Close Company Open Company
